A Guide to the Edward H. Peeples, Jr. Papers, n.d. 1910, 1943-1994
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Social Dimensions of Kentucky Counties, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- South Carolinians Speak - A Moderate Approach to Race Relations, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Southern Schools: Progress and Problems, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Southern Schools Token Desegregation and Beyond, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Stormtrooper Magazine, The 1965 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Teachers for our Big City Schools, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Toward a Multi-Racial Society, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Toward Equality: Baltimore's Progress Report, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Unfinished Revolution, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- United Nations and the Population Problems, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Urban Universities: Rhetoric, Reality, and Conflict, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- What Price Integration?, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- When a City Closes its Schools, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Who is a Jew? A Reader, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Why Racial Integration is a Crime and Why it will destroy the United States if Not Repealed, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- You and a Health Career, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- You and Segregation, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Your Right to Indian Welfare, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 45)